Hey! Usopp! Are you there?
Where did you run out to? Come back!
Hey! Usopp!
I'll be up here for sure.
Where are you hiding?
Are you in there? Usopp!
Seriously, I just saw him!
Hey, they're calling you. No, I can't.
It's too soon.
Stop playing hide-and-seek!
Get out here or I'll kick your ass!
Kick your ass!
Hey, do you know where
it was up at Sniper King?
You're his friend, right?
Oh, uh, no need to fear.
He took a different boat and
went on ahead by himself.
But why?
That doesn't make sense.
The Mary's his ship, right?
You gotta be kidding me.
If they haven't figured it out
yet, then what's it gonna take?
Not here, either.
What the heck is going on?
I checked everywhere.
Looks like we're the
only ones on the ship.
That's pretty strange.
The Mary didn't sail itself here, did it?
Of course not.
Someone was calling us.
The whole crew heard it.
And you don't know who it was? No.
Just a voice beckoning us to the sea.
Come on, you guys.
The answer here is obvious.
I'm telling you, that was
Mary's voice we heard.
Huh?
You think so?
Mary, come on!
Say something else!
I think we'd know by now
if the ship could talk.
You know, as ridiculous as it may
sound, I was thinking the same thing.
But there's no way, right?
That's impossible.
Hey, look, there's a ship coming! What?
Who is it?
I can see the Straw Hat!
I knew they'd make it!
I just knew it!
It's a galley log company ship.
I thought they were done for when
they went out during Aqualaguna!
Forget Aqualaguna!
They survived Enies Lobby!
Ha-ha-ha! Ahoy!
What's up, Icebox?
Nice surprise, huh?
Nico Robin survived.
Hmm.
They pulled it off after all.
They took on the world government and won.
Ha-ha-ha! Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
They lost it all, and then
they brought it all back.
Barry!
Their ship! It's breaking!
Hey, why is it falling
apart all of a sudden?
There's nothing sudden about it.
We all knew this was inevitable.
They told us, right?
Before we left, they said
Mary was unfit to sail.
Yeah, but...
What happened to you, Mary?
Ice Puffs, help!
Mary's in trouble!
Can't you do something?
You got here just in time!
You're all shipwrights, aren't you?
I'm begging you!
Don't let her die now!
Mary's more than just a ship!
She's a member of our crew!
If it wasn't for her, we all
would have died back there!
So come on, do something!
She's fought hard for you.
But it's time to let her rest.
Besides, I've already done
everything that I can.
What's that noise?
Someone on Scrap Island?
Wait a second.
This is the Strawhead ship.
Aqua Laguna did quite a number on it.
It's a wreck.
No, this is from long before that.
I want to sail.
What was that voice?
I want to sail one last time.
What am I doing?
There's no hope for this ship.
Mr. Iceberg!
You gotta get out of there!
Another tidal wave's about to hit!
Thank you.
Oh, I'm ready, you ship.
The weather's still too rough out there.
Then I'll go alone.
Are you kidding? No,
no. We'll go with you!
This is a miracle.
There's no other word for it.
The miracle of a ship that's gone beyond
its limits to see you one last time.
As you know, I've been a
shipwright for many years.
But I've never seen a ship
as incredible as this one.
It's lived a wonderful life.
Let's go back, everyone?
Back to the seas of adventure!
Mary!
I came to get you
I understand.
Well, guys, you ready?
Yeah.
Mary, I know the floor of the
sea is a dark and lonely place,
but don't worry, we're
here to see you off.
I'm sure you wish you was here, but it's
probably best that Usopp isn't around.
I don't know if you can take this.
Well, is that true?
Of course it isn't.
We must all say our farewells someday.
Every man knows that.
We must hold back our tears.
Luffy knows what has to be done.
Thank you for carrying us for
so long and for so far, Barry.
Snow?
The real Carabelle!
Yeah!
Now the going Mary has
everything she can possibly need!
Cheers to a new ship and a new Gourmet!
Look at all the damage
you did to poor Mary!
The crew has to take care of its ship!
And don't you forget it!
Right, we're sorry!
Hey, Luffy, what's so loud down there?
Cannon firing practice!
Then it's not going very well.
Let the expert aim the thing!
Blossom!
You hit that on the first try!
Uh, whatcha think?
So are you impressed yet?
I'm going to the Grand
Line to find the all-blue.
I'm going to be King of the Pirates.
The world's best swordsman.
I'm going so I can draw
a map of the whole world.
I'm going to be a brave
warrior of the sea.
And now, to the Grand Line!
The entrance to the
Grand Line is a mountain!
We made it!
I can see it!
This is the greatest
sea in the whole world!
The Grand Law!
Let's go!
Ha ha ha!
We're flying!
Don't bother looking back, cause
we're going straight ahead!
I'm afraid there's
nowhere left for me to go.
And for that matter, there's no
place for me to return to either.
So I've decided to stay here with you.
I see your problem.
Guess there's no other choice.
Welcome.
Hooray!
Trust me, I'm a navigator, aren't I?
We're flying!
Yeah!
We're headed to the sky!
There it is!
Sky Island!
I can't believe it.
I can't
believe
it.
No!
I'm sorry.
I wanted to carry everyone
just a little bit further.
I had so much fun.
I wish our adventures would never end.
Mary!
Who is that?
But I'm sorry, I... No, Mary!
If anyone should apologize,
it's us, not you!
I'm no good at steering!
I ran you into icebergs
and all kinds of stuff!
I took bad care of you
and ripped your sails!
Zoro and Sanji are idiots too.
They were breaking your
stuff all the time.
Usopp tried to fix you, but
he wasn't any good at it.
We all know that.
If anyone sorry, it's us.
I don't mind.
I was happy.
I know you always treated me with love.
Thank you.
Even if the time we
spent together was short,
I'm glad that I could spend it with you.
Mary!